KELLY WEI JIN

CONTACT

778-325-9156

kellywj01@gmail.com

1-7151 Moffatt Rd. Richmond, BC Canada

EDUCATION

RICHMOND SECONDARY SCHOOL 2018-2023

International Baccalaureate Diploma Final grade 40/45

UNIVERSITY OF BRITISH COLUMBIA

2023-Present

Bachelor of Science with intended Computer Science specialization

SKILLS

Web Development (HTML, CSS, Javascript)

Java

SwiftUI, XCode

Graphic Design (Canva, Adobe Illustrator,

Adobe Photoshop)

Wireframe Creation (Figma)

Leadership

Organization

Communication

Collaboration

ABOUT ME

I am a first year university student with a passion for taking on challenges and broadening my knowledge through unique opportunities. With years of work and volunteer experience, my creative and collaboration skills have helped me connect meaningfully with others along the way. I am greatly interested in any opportunity to expand my skillset and work with new people!

WORK EXPERIENCE

PIANO TEACHER (2016-2018)

Self-Employed

- Taught children piano techniques and musical pieces in preparation for the Royal Conservatory of Music (RCM) piano examinations
- Adopted a friendly teaching style and communicated regularly with parents regarding their child's progress

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

MATH TUTOR (JAN 2022-AUG 2022)

Youth Initiative Vancouver

- Taught key mathematical concepts to young students according to the BC Mathematics Curriculum
- Created lesson plans, study material, and graded homework for each class

AMBASSADOR PROGRAM DIRECTOR (APR 2021-JUN 2023)

Frontline Immunity

- Coordinated seasonal Ambassador Program sessions by recruiting students, communicating with workshop facilitators, and creating educational content for social media platforms to increase vaccine literacy
- Trained 500+ student ambassadors, with 200+ schools represented

AWARDS

BC EXCELLENCE SCHOLARSHIP AWARD

2023

BC Ministry of Education

PRINCIPAL'S HONOUR ROLL 2018-2023

Richmond Secondary School

SUBJECT EXCELLENCE AWARDS

Richmond Secondary School

IB English 12 (2023)

IB ITGS 12 (2023)

IB English 11 Critical Analysis (2022)

Career and Life Education 10 (2021)

Physical & Health Education 10 (2021)

Chemistry 11 (2021)

28TH PLACE IN CANADA DISTINCTION AWARD 2022

Waterloo Avogadro Chemistry Exam

TOP 25% DISTINCTION AWARD 2020

Waterloo Beaver Computing Challenge

2ND PLACE PIANO SENIOR DIVISION

2017

Vancouver Kiwanis Music Festival

GRAPHIC DESIGN INTERN (MAR 2022-JUN 2023)

The Coding Foundation

- Created appealing infographics, posters, and promotional content for social media platforms to engage community members and reach a greater demographic
- Managed social media accounts and organized events with partner organizations

INTERNAL HUMAN RESOURCES REPRESENTATIVE (AUG 2020-SEPT 2021)

NeuroHealth BC

- Conducted seasonal hiring rounds and interviews for various committees within the organization
- Took committee-specific meeting minutes and sent out reminders for task items accordingly
- Organized and facilitated monthly team bonding events to foster a friendly and tight-knit community within the organization